facefucking.com 2019-03-04

# Customer Support Center - Privacy Statement

### Privacy Notice:

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your personal information is collected and used. A link to this notice can be found on every page and website within our network. 

### The Information We Collect:

Each time you visit any one of the DPEt pMPunlItYiEmUeQdRijaF BLxttdi.y websites, we will collect your host / IP address, cookies, and a record of the website which referred you. 

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on DPEt pMPunlItYiEmUeQdRijaF BLxttdi.y operated websites. On some pages, you can order products/subscriptions, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

First Name:  
Last Name:  
Address:  
E-mail address:  
Phone number:  
State/Province:  
Country:

We DO NOT collect billing information, such as credit card numbers.

### The Way We Use Information:

DPEt pMPunlItYiEmUeQdRijaF BLxttdi.y collects account registration information on its web site. This is done to help us provide our visitors and clients with the best service and with valuable information regarding relevant products and services from DPEt pMPunlItYiEmUeQdRijaF BLxttdi.y and appropriate third parties. DPEt pMPunlItYiEmUeQdRijaF BLxttdi.y is always dedicated to protecting personal information and will make every reasonable effort to handle collected information appropriately. All relevant information collected, as well as related requests, will be handled as carefully and efficiently as possible in accordance with DPEt pMPunlItYiEmUeQdRijaF BLxttdi.y 's standards for integrity and objectivity. 

### Our Commitment To Data Security:

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

Have a question? Contact Support!
